

# ANDRI KAREL JÚLÍUSSON

### PROFILE

I am a 24 year old that lives in Hafnarfjörður. I graduated with a Bsc in computer science from Reykjavík University. My interest include programming,music,traveling and video games. I am enthusiastic and quick to learn new things. I like working with others . I am interested in a working environment where i can grow career wise as well as a person.

6167926

andrikarel@gmail.com

www.andrikarel.com

O Arnarhraun 20, Hafnarfjörður

## SKILLS

Web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, React, .Net

Programming Languages C, C++, C#, Java, Python, SQL

> Tools REST, Agile, Git, Linux

> > Languages Icelandic, English

### EDUCATION

#### **BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Reykjavík University - Reykjavík | 2015 - 2018

### **DIPLOMA (STÚDENTSPRÓF)**

Flensborg - Hafnarfjörður | 2010 - 2014

### EXPERIENCE

### PROGRAMMER (INTERNSHIP)

//Jökulá - Reykjavík | 3 months

- Final project for Reykjavík University.
- The project was to create a full stack web application that handles supervision of projects that employees of //Jökulá were working on
- Implemented using Node.js
- The application is used in-house at //Jökulá.

#### **RECEPTIONIST / BARTENDER**

Hotel Klettur - Reykjavík | 2012 - present

- Assisting guests with various problems
- Giving information to guests
- Handiling invoices and hotel reservations using Microsoft Navision
- Working the bar at evenings
- Mixing various drinks for guests

### **REFERENCE**

Kristján Jóhann Kristjánsson Assistant hotel manager

P: 770-4142

E: kristjan@hotelklettur.com

### KITCHEN WORKER

Hotel Klettur - Reykjavik | 2011 - 2012

- Preparing breakfast for hotel guests
- Cleaning

### PACKAGING (SUMMER JOB)

Sælgætisverksmiðja Góa - Hafnarfjörður | 2009

Packaging candy